ABDELRHMAN AHMED ELNHAS

FRONTEND DEVELOPER | UI/UX DESIGNER | GRAPHIC DESIGNER abdelrhman.elnhas1@gmail.com | (+20) 106-927-7066 | abdelrhman-elnhas.netlify.app | Alexandria, Egypt

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am **Frontend Web Developer** since 2021. I've worked on several projects in various fields. Also, I gained some knowledge about **Backend Web Development** during working on projects. I am also a **UI/UX Designer** and a **Senior Graphic Designer**. I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for technology, especially programming.

Contact Information

Portfolio: https://abdelrhman-elnhas.netlify.app/

Linkedin : https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdelrhman-elnhas

• Behance: https://www.behance.net/aedesigns11

Github: https://github.com/abdelrhman-elnhas/

• Gmail: Abdelrhman.elnhas1@gmail.com

Whatsapp: +201069277066

EDUCATION

Degree in Computer Engineering, Faculty of Engineering, Kafr Elsheikh University

07/2023

Computer and Control Systems Department.

Projects

- cropcopter.net
- drsherifwaly.com
- abdelrhman-elnhas.netlify.app
- francaisbacessam.com
- alemlak-almonofy.com
- dolphin-in-biology.com
- elawaiel.com
- mahmoudabdelgader.com

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React.JS
- API
- SASS
- UI Design

- Python
- VCS (Git & Github)
- Laravel
- MySQL
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Master Code | Kafr Elsheikh, Egypt

Frontend Developer | 04/2021 - 07/2023

- Worked on multiple educational websites like :
 - o https://francaisbacessam.com
 - https://drsherifwaly.com
 - o https://mahmoudabdelqader.com
 - https://alemlak-almonofy.com
 - https://dolphin-in-biology.com
 - http://elawaiel.com

Master Code | Kafr Elsheikh, Egypt UI/UX Designer | 06/2022 – 05/2023

- Master Code Landing Page UI/UX Design
 - https://www.behance.net/gallery/160989575/MasterCode-Website-UIUX-Design
- NileICT Landing Page UI/UX Design
 - https://www.behance.net/gallery/152832487/Nile-ICT-UIUX-Design
- All Traders Mobile App UI/UX Design
 - o https://www.behance.net/gallery/183936541/All-Traders-Mobile-App-UIUX-Design
- CropCopter Website UI/UX Design
 - https://www.behance.net/gallery/183936663/CropCopter-Website-UIUX-Design

The Sparks Foundation Internship

Web Developer Intern | 02/2023 - 03/2023

AE Adv. | ElMahalla Elkubra, Egypt

Graphic Designer | 04/2014 - Present

- Responsible for designing social media designs, logos and all types of advertising printing materials.
 - https://www.behance.net/aedesigns11

CERTIFICATIONS

Web-Development Internship, The Sparks Foundation	02/2023
Figma like a pro mixed with UI/UX, Udemy	10/2023
Version Control, Meta	01/2023
Skills Verification Test for Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), HackerRank	12/2022
Git & Github, 365 Data Science	12/2022
Introduction to Python, 365 Data Science	12/2022
Introduction to Frontend Development, Meta	04/2023
UX Design Fundamentals, MaharaTech - ITIMooca	12/2022
HTML and CSS in Depth, Meta	06/2023
React Basics, Meta	08/2023
Introduction to Backend Development, Meta	01/2023
Programming with JavaScript, Meta	05/2023
Introduction to Databases for Backend Development, Meta	04/2023
Programming in Python, Meta	03/2023
JavaScript, Sololearn	12/2022
Responsive Web Design, Sololearn	12/2022
CSS, Sololearn	12/2022
Web Development Fundamentals, Sololearn	12/2022
EF SET	03/2020